A Guide to the Randolph Family Papers, 1866-1900
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Randolph Family Papers 1866-1900
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
572
This collection consists of 1,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the University Library as a gift on 26 July 1939.
Scope and Content
Papers relating to the Randolph family of Louisa County, Va. and Culpeper County, Va., Baltimore, Md., and New York (State?). Includes ms. ledger of M.P. Randolph with C.B. Payne.
Contents List
- Letters of W. H. Payne 1859, 4 items. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1860-1864, 42 items. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1865-1869, 35 items. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1870-1875, 53 items. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1875, n.d., 54 items. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1876-1878, 48 items. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1878-1879, 43 items. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1880-1884, 50 items. (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1885-1889, 48 items. (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1890-1899, n.d., 28 items. (Box 2)
- Business Correspondence 1856-1888, 51 item. (Box 2)
- Business Correspondence 1889-1893, n.d., 57 items. (Box 2)
- Correspondence n.d., 57 items. (Box 2)
- Correspondence n.d., 69 items. (Box 3)
- Correspondence n.d., 57 items. (Box 3)
- Postcards 1884-1891, n.d., 82 items. (Box 3)
- Financial and Legal Papers 1870-1892, 20 items. (Box 3)
- Ledger of M. P. Randolph 1889-1890, 1 item. (Box 3)
- Daybook 1849, 1 item. (Box 3)
- Memoranda Book 1868, 1 item. (Box 3)
- Newspaper Clippings 1863, n.d., 6 items. (Box 3)
- Printed Material 1870-1890, n.d., 35 items. (Box 3)
- Campaign and Inauguration Ribbons 1884-1885, 2 items. (Box 3)
- Invitations 1886-1891, n.d., 10 items. (Box 3)
- Certificate of Lieutenancy issued to Shirley P. Randolph 1890, 1 item. (Box 3)
- Poetry and a short story n.d., 7 items. (Box 3)
- Genealogical Material n.d., 2 items. (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous n.d., 12 items. (Box 3)